# Rhett Brink

Kerrville, TX 78028 / Rhett.brink16@icloud.com / (830) 890-0727

https://krodin98.github.io/Rhett.github.io/

(My personal website I made to showcase projects and highlight my resume)

## **Summary Statement**

I am a highly motivated college graduate with thorough knowledge of computer hardware and software stemming from personal interest and experience with computer software in the form of multiple programming languages, Windows, Apple, Linux operating systems, and applications. I also developed excellent interpersonal as well as communication skills that I'm wishing to apply towards my career as a software engineer.

#### Education

- Majored in Computer Programming
- Bachelor's Degree in Computer Information Technology with a focus on Computer Programming
- Schreiner University, Kerrville, TX
- → Relevant Coursework
- Software development
- Client Solutions
- Debugging
- Reporting

Key skills and Competencies

- Programming languages are -
- → Python
- → F#
- → C++
- $\rightarrow$  Java
- $\rightarrow$  SQL
- Developing/assisting in the development of software
- Windows operating system
- Linux operating system
- Computer hardware knowledge
- Excellent Communication skills and Team player
- Excruciating attention to detail

### Work Experience

- Home Depot Appliance Specialist and Cashier 6/2020 to 1/2021 Kerrville, TX
- → Handling transactions for a wide variety of high dollar appliances.
- → Thoroughly assisting customers with whatever they needed.
- → Provided customers with an enjoyable, stress-free experience.
- → Always providing outstanding customer service.
- → Navigated a complicated and outdated computer system.
- Hobby Lobby Cashier and Package Handler 5/2022 to 9/2022 Kerrville, TX
- → Provided customers with an enjoyable, stress-free experience.
- → Assist my fellow associates with whatever needs to be done
- → Quickly remove freight from the delivery trucks and efficiently sort it
- Peterson Regional Medical Center Tech 1 (Intern) 2/2023 to 8/2023 Kerrville, TX
- → Assisted in IT support tasks, troubleshooting hardware and software issues.
- → Provided technical assistance to hospital staff, ensuring minimal workflow disruptions.
- → Gained hands-on experience with hospital IT systems and cybersecurity protocols.
- → Effectively managed and documented IT support tickets.
- → Adapted to a fast-paced healthcare environment while maintaining attention to detail.

# Honors/Awards and Accomplishments

- Member of honor society Alpha Chi
- Member of honor society Alpha Sigma Lambda

- GPA 4.0
- GRADUATED SUMMA CUM LAUDE
- VALEDICTORIAN FINALIST
- Presidents List
- VOLUNTEER WORK